export const ScienceMedium = [
  {
    question: "Which animal never drinks water in its entire life?",
    Options: ["Kangaroo", "Hippopotamus", "Rat", "Kangaroo rat"],
    correct: 4,
    marked: -1
  },
  {
    question: "What is the physical phase of life called?",
    Options: ["Protoplasm", "Cytoplasm", "Organelles", "None of the above"],
    correct: 1,
    marked: -1
  },
  {
    question: "The largest cell is ________________",
    Options: ["Nerve Cell", "Ovum", "The egg of an Ostrich", "None of the above"],
    correct: 3,
    marked: -1
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the following compound is mainly used in hand sanitizer?",
    Options: ["Aldehyde", "Acetic acid", "Alcohol", "Ketone"],
    correct: 3,
    marked: -1
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the following quantity increases in a group when we move from top to bottom?",
    Options: ["Valency", "Electronegativity", "Atomic size", "Ionization energy"],
    correct: 3,
    marked: -1
  },
  {
    question: "What is the name of the cells in the body that engulf foreign particles like bacteria?",
    Options: ["Phagocytes", "Globulin", "Fibrinogen", "Albumin"],
    correct: 1,
    marked: -1
  },
  {
    question: "There are _____ number of muscles in human.",
    Options: ["638", "637", "639", "640"],
    correct: 3,
    marked: -1
  },
  {
    question: "What is the life span of RBC?",
    Options: ["130 days", "110 days", "100 days", "120 days"],
    correct: 4,
    marked: -1
  },
  {
    question: "What is the life span of WBC?",
    Options: ["2-15 days", "3-15 days", "4-15 days", "5-20 days"],
    correct: 1,
    marked: -1
  },
  {
    question: "Which is the vertebrate that has two chambered heart?",
    Options: ["Fish", "Snake", "Blue Whale", "Crocodile"],
    correct: 1,
    marked: -1
  },
  {
    question: "_________________ is the longest cell.",
    Options: ["Nerve Cell", "Skin", "Spleen", "None of the above"],
    correct: 1,
    marked: -1
  },
  {
    question: "The number of ribs in a human body is _____.",
    Options: ["23", "24", "25", "22"],
    correct: 2,
    marked: -1
  },
  {
    question: "Which is the smallest flightless bird?",
    Options: ["Kiwi", "Penguin", "Ostrich", "Rhea"],
    correct: 1,
    marked: -1
  },
  {
    question: "Saurology is the study of ___________.",
    Options: ["Mosquitoes", "Snake", "Lizards", "Cockroach"],
    correct: 3,
    marked: -1
  },
  {
    question: "Hormones are produced by _____________.",
    Options: ["Endocrine glands", "Pituitary glands", "Hypothalamus", "Pancreas"],
    correct: 1,
    marked: -1
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the following is the ‘master gland’?",
    Options: ["Thymus gland", "Pancreas", "Pineal gland", "Pituitary gland"],
    correct: 4,
    marked: -1
  },
  {
    question: "What is the full form of ADH?",
    Options: ["Anti Diuretic Hormone", "Adhesive Diuretic Hormone", "Acidic Diuretic Hormone", "Adenosine Double Hormoneeicharcoal"],
    correct: 1,
    marked: -1
  },
  {
    question: "What is the normal value of blood sugar in the body?",
    Options: ["80 to 120mg/100 ml of blood", "70 to 120mg/100 ml of blood", "90 to 120mg/100 ml of blood", "60 to 120mg/100 ml of blood"],
    correct: 1,
    marked: -1
  },
  {
    question: "Which is the largest blood vessel in the body?",
    Options: ["Alveoli", "Artery", "Aorta", "Vein"],
    correct: 3,
    marked: -1
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the following carries impure blood?",
    Options: ["Pulmonary artery", "Pulmonary vein", "Alveoli", "Aorta"],
    correct: 1,
    marked: -1
  },
  {
    question: "Who had performed the world’s first heart transplant?",
    Options: ["Dr. Venugopal", "William Harvey", "Christian Bernard", "None of the above"],
    correct: 3,
    marked: -1
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the following is not an allotrope of Carbon?",
    Options: ["Diamond", "Graphite", "Fullerenes", "Glass"],
    correct: 4,
    marked: -1
  },
  {
    question: "What is the formula of Sulfuric acid?",
    Options: ["H2SO4", "SO2", "Na2SO4", "K2SO4"],
    correct: 1,
    marked: -1
  },
  {
    question: "How are the following elements arranged in the Periodic table? H, He, Li, Be and B",
    Options: ["H, He, Li, Be and B", "H, Li, He, Be and B", "H, He, Be, Li and B", "H, Be, He, B and Li"],
    correct: 1,
    marked: -1
  },
  {
    question: "What is the number of periods in which Periodic table is divided?",
    Options: ["6", "7", "8", "9"],
    correct: 2,
    marked: -1
  },
];

